peejeshare.com 2019-02-26

# Hostwinds Privacy Policy | Hostwinds

### PROMISE

HOSTWINDS.COM is committed to maintaining your trust and confidence. The following online privacy policy is intended to protect and secure the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified) you provide to us online.

In addition, HOSTWINDS.COM will not send you emails you have not agreed to receive. We may periodically send you emails announcing news and event information. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from us as well.

### NO SHARING POLICY

HOSTWINDS.COM will never sell, rent, lease, or exchange your personal information with other organizations. HOSTWINDS.COM assures you that the identity of all who contact us through this website will be kept confidential.

### SECURITY

HOSTWINDS.COM is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the proper use of information, we have established and implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

HOSTWINDS.COM uses Internet Encryption Software, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Protocol, when collecting or transferring sensitive data, such as credit card information. Any information you enter is encrypted at your browser, sent over the public Internet in encrypted form, and then de-encrypted at our server. Once we receive your credit card information, it it accessible only to a small number of trusted HOSTWINDS.COM employees who have been specially trained in processing this information.

### COOKIES

From time to time, we may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive or read cookie files created by other websites.

Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to recognize you when you return to our sites, or to identify which areas of our network of websites you have visited (i,e, e-commerce sites, etc.). We may use this information to better personalize the content you see on our sites.

Many websites place cookies on your hard drive. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Your browser can refuse all cookies or show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

### CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY

We are concerned about the privacy of young children and do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We encourage you to become involved in your child's access to the Internet and to our site in order to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected.

To read more about online safety and how to become more involved with your child's online experience, visit the Federal Trade Commission website. You may also benefit from the information and resources available on ProtectKids.com.

### BILLING POLICY

We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover, and American Express. All online orders are processed through 128 bit SSL encryption to protect your credit card information during your online transaction. All prices and figures are listed in US Dollars.

### RETURN POLICY

See our Guarantees page for our return guarantees.

### ACCOUNT POLICY

HOSTWINDS.COM reserves the right to deactivate or remove any user account provided by www.hostwinds.com without notice if the user has provided wrong information or violated common Internet policies, or if the account has been inactive for more than 60 days.

### DOWNLOAD LICENSE

Downloads are solely for personal, non commercial use. Copies of a download can only be stored on computers or devices owned by the person or entity that purchased the download. Additional licenses of downloads can be purchased from www.hostwinds.com.

### CONTACTING US

Please contact us if you have comments or questions about any of our policies or our website. For information about your payment or order, please contact us at 1-206-866-0665. We are available by phone 24/7/365.

Our mailing address is:  
12101 Tukwila International Blvd   
3rd Floor, Suite 320   
Seattle, WA 98168   
206-886-0665
